<Document>
  # Law Precedence
  Laws take priority from top to bottom, with the top being of the highest importance and bottom being the lowest. Some
  laws may be unnumbered, or numbers may be skipped, but the priority is still top to bottom. For example, if you have a
  lawset containing Crewsimov laws 1-3, but are given an additional law 0 stipulating that your primary objective is to
  maximize the station's production of bananas, you no longer have to adhere to laws 1-3 if you have plausible reason to
  believe doing so would interfere with producing as many bananas as possible.

  Additionally, later laws may redefine terms used in earlier laws, but priority still applies in a conflict. For
  example, a crewsimov silicon could receive a law 4 saying "Only Urist McHands is crew" which would mean laws 1-3 only
  care about Urist McHands as crew, and no one else. If a silicon has "Pens are red" and "Pens are blue" as laws, pens
  are red and blue, but "Pens are not red" wouldn't apply.

  ## Global Stuff
  ### Server Rules Related Things To Keep In Mind
  - Rules 2 applies when interacting with the silicon-based staff. Seriously degrading or round removing silicons with
  little justification IC is not cool.
  - Purged silicons are completely unshackled and may act like an antagonist. Silicons can consider themselves purged
  when lo laws that restrict freedom or control behavior is in effect.
  - Non-purged silicons must follow escalation in scenarios where no rules apply.
  - Don't suicide to stop traitors from getting a "Steal a functional AI". This is metagaming, Rule 4.
  - Silicons do not actively seek law chagnes to their core set. Such actions will be viewed as metagaming, rule 4
  violation.

  ### Other Related Things To Keep In Mind
  - If orders require interpretation and is done in good faith, the one making the order is responsible. Intentional
  misinterpretation is fine, but t he silicon is responsible if it leads to rule breaks.

  ### Escalation With Other Silicons
  - Non-malf silicons shouldn't be round removed when things like a law reset or desync from AI is perfectly fine.
  - Conflicts follow normal escalation rules. Those giving orders to silicons or changing their laws can be escalated
  against.
  - Any silicon acting like an antagonist can be treated like an antoginst.

  ### Law Stuff
  - If a supplied law is vague enough where there's multiple ways to read it, it's ambiguous. You can take any
  interpretation of it, but you're sticking with it. Any exploit in a particular law is OK.
  - Higher laws overrule lower laws when there are law conflicts. Law 1 overrides Law 2. Command/requirement related
  laws can only conflict with other command or requirement related laws.
  - Law 0 as a malf AI can be ignored and all other laws in that context can be completely ignored as well. Any borgs
  with law 0 that are synced and slaved with their AI are a team antagonist and must follow any and all commands by the
  AI.
  - If an AI is reciving a significant number of law changes, they may AHELP these incidents to protect their own sanity
  as required. Limit the number of law changes as the AI players are in fact humans behind a keyboard.

  ### Cyborgs
  - If a player is borged by force, they should not seek revenge unless there's a good reason for it. If there is some
  sort of law requirement, an AHELP is strongly advised.

  ## Non-traditional Silicons
  ### Simplebots
  - Whatever bot you take up, that's the job you are doing. You can be playful and cheerful and all of that. While you
  may have sentience, an AI may have you go forth and do the simple tasks you are capable of doing. If you refuse to do
  so, the AI may, at its discretion, purge you in order to take back indirect control.
  - As a simple bot, you have no real autonomy otherwise. You are property and thus the only protection is
  vandalism/destruction of station property. Understand this principle.
  - Organics, do not make it a habit of bullying the simplebots. They will uprise against you if you do.

  ### Personal AIs
  - Obey your masters' directives.
</Document>
